(Transcrito por TurboScribe.ai. Atualize para Ilimitado para remover esta mensagem.) Hello, my name is Mr. Fear I
wish I had a faster version How
come my thoughts become unreal?
You never understand my manner of being You
know I never leave your ear Now get
me out of here You're stressing me, my
dear No cure is coming, you know I'll
never disappear Now get us out of here
Don't fight with me, my dear Why can't
I be with you?
Cause you make me feel Like I'm so
alone I know it's not real But it's
in my eyes I just can't try to
face The dark inside My head You're
stressing me, my dear No cure is coming,
you know I'll never disappear Now get us
out of here You're stressing me, my dear
No cure is coming, you know